<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Charleston Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="category_eat">Eat</string>
    <string name="category_play">Play</string>
    <string name="category_stay">Stay</string>
    <string name="category_shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="category_tour">Tour</string>
    <string name="charleston">Charleston, SC</string>
    <string name="about_charleston">About Charleston</string>
    <!-- Info from charlestoncvb.com -->
    <string name="city">Charleston is the oldest and largest city in South Carolina.
        It was founded in 1670 as Charles Towne in honor of King Charles II of England.
        Charleston is known for its rich history, incredible architecture, amazing restaurants,
        and famous southern hospitality. Charleston has received many accolades, including
        being voted the #1 city in the United States by Conde Nast Traveler for the last
        several years. Charleston has also been named America\'s Most Friendly City several times.
        Southern Living Magazine calls Charleston the most polite and hospitable city in America.</string>
    <string name="sky">Blue Sky</string>
    <string name="homes">Charleston Homes on the Beach</string>
    <string name="weather_in_charleston">Weather in Charleston</string>
    <string name="seasons">SPRING\nAverage temperatures: 58°F to 72°F\nSpring is the Charleston
        area\'s most spectacular time of the year. From early March into early June, enjoy the
        vibrant colors of azaleas, dogwoods and other flowers in bloom.\n\nSUMMER\nAverage
        temperatures: 78°F to 82°F\nThe Charleston region\'s warm, sultry summers are punctuated
        by cooling coastal breezes and passing afternoon thunderstorms - all of which invite
        visitors to slow down, sip something refreshing and relax for a while.\n\nAUTUMN\nAverage
        temperatures: 58°F to 76°F\nAutumn in the Charleston region brings with it days of bright
        sunshine, clear blue skies, golden marshes and perfectly crisp evenings.\n\nWINTER\nAverage
        temperatures: 47°F to 52°F\nTypically mild, winters in the Charleston region are cool with
        periods of rain and the chance of snow flurries come late December or early January.</string>
    <string name="image_of_item">Image of Item</string>
    <string name="dividing_bar">Dividing Bar</string>
    <string name="halls">Halls Chophouse</string>
    <string name="halls_address">434 King Street\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="halls_phone">(843) 727–0090</string>
    <string name="halls_info">Halls Chophouse is a family steakhouse restaurant located in the
        Upper King District of Charleston. As a premier steakhouse they use the finest freshest
        USDA prime steaks and meat. Vegan and vegetarian dishes are specially made upon request.
        Halls Chophouse also provides gluten free menu options and fresh sustainable local seafood
        dishes.</string>
    <string name="halls_website">www.hallschophouse.com</string>
    <string name="fig">FIG</string>
    <string name="fig_address">232 Meeting Street\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="mccradys">McCrady\'s</string>
    <string name="mccradys_address">155 East Bay Street\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="fig_phone">(843) 805–5900</string>
    <string name="mccradys_phone">(843) 577–0025</string>
    <string name="fig_website">www.eatatfig.com</string>
    <string name="mccradys_website">www.mccradysrestaurant.com</string>
    <string name="fig_info">At the core, FIG’s menu is a labor of love. We source products with
        integrity, flavor and soul, and incorporate these seasonal offerings into our menu nightly.
        The result is food that is honest, straightforward and pays homage to the Lowcountry,
        a special place we are privileged to call home.</string>
    <string name="mccradys_info">McCrady’s is a tasting menu-only restaurant helmed by James Beard
        Award winning Chef Sean Brock. The 22-seat space, located in historic downtown Charleston,
        features exceptional hospitality and an open kitchen creating an intimate and adventurous
        dining experience at South Carolina’s only AAA five diamond awarded restaurant.</string>
    <string name="lighthouse">Morris Island Lighthouse Eco-Cruise</string>
    <string name="waterfront">Riley Waterfront Park</string>
    <string name="aquarium">South Carolina Aquarium</string>
    <string name="lighthouse_address">1871 Bowens Island Road\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="waterfront_address">1 Vendue Range, Concord Street\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="aquarium_address">100 Aquarium Wharf Street\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="lighthouse_phone">(843) 795–0330</string>
    <string name="waterfront_phone">(843) 724–7327</string>
    <string name="aquarium_phone">(843) 577–3474</string>
    <string name="lighthouse_website">www.charlestonoutdooradventures.com</string>
    <string name="waterfront_website">www.charlestonparksconservancy.org/park/riley-waterfront-park</string>
    <string name="aquarium_website">www.scaquarium.org/</string>
    <string name="lighthouse_info">The uninhabited Morris Island makes a nice contrast to the nearby
        city of Charleston, but Morris Island isn’t easy to get to, as it’s only accessible by boat.
        This cruise sets sail from Bowens Island and takes you to Morris Island to spend free time
        exploring it at your own pace before heading back. Be on the lookout for marine life, such
        as bottlenose dolphins and sea turtles, from the boat.</string>
    <string name="waterfront_info">Riley Waterfront Park is one of the peninsula\'s most visited
        parks, centrally located near The Market. Finished in 1990, Waterfront Park is a favorite
        of visitors and locals alike, offering fantastic views of the Charleston harbor.
        Old-fashioned park benches dot the park, and family-sized swings offer a fun way to spend
        a relaxing afternoon together.</string>
    <string name="aquarium_info">Fun, wonder and education come together at the South Carolina
        Aquarium. See a rare albino American alligator, get hands-on at the Touch Tank, marvel
        at the sharks in the Great Ocean Tank, come face-to-face with rays in the Shallows, or
        see our brand new state-of-the-art sea turtle hospital in the new Zucker Family Sea Turtle
        Recovery experience.</string>
    <string name="farmers">Charleston Farmers Market</string>
    <string name="market">Historic City Market</string>
    <string name="shops">Shops at Charleston Place</string>
    <string name="farmers_address">Marion Square\n329 Meeting Street\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="market_address">188 Meeting Street\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="shops_address">205 Meeting Street\nCharleston, SC 29401</string>
    <string name="farmers_phone">(843) 509–3619</string>
    <string name="market_phone">(843) 937–0920</string>
    <string name="shops_phone">(888) 722–4900</string>
    <string name="farmers_website">www.charlestonfarmersmarket.com</string>
    <string name="market_website">www.thecharlestoncitymarket.com</string>
    <string name="shops_website">www.charlestonplaceshops.com</string>
    <string name="farmers_info">The CFM is dedicated to the support and advocacy of Lowcountry
        farmers, growers, prepared/packaged food, artisans, crafters, live performers and community
        groups of all kinds. We offer a variety of local produce, plants, herbs and cut flowers as
        well as breakfast and lunch vendors, live entertainment and an assortment of juried arts
        and crafts from local artisans.</string>
    <string name="market_info">The Charleston City Market is one of the nation\'s oldest public
        markets and the cultural heart of Charleston. We are home to more than 300 vibrant
        entrepreneurs, and we are open every day of the year except December 25th. No matter what
        time of day or season you plan to visit, there is something to see, do, taste, and take
        home as a souvenir from the Charleston City Market!</string>
    <string name="shops_info">From L\'Occitane to Louis Vuitton, The Shops at Belmond Charleston
        Place are an exclusive collection of world-famous stores nestled in the heart of
        Charleston\'s downtown shopping district. There\'s something for everyone. Go ahead and
        treat yourself.</string>
    <string name="francis">Francis Marion Hotel</string>
    <string name="pavilion">Market Pavilion Hotel</string>
    <string name="wentworth">Wentworth Mansion</string>
    <string name="francis_address">387 King Street\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="pavilion_address">225 East Bay Street\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="wentworth_address">149 Wentworth Street\nCharleston, SC 29401</string>
    <string name="francis_phone">(843) 722–0600</string>
    <string name="pavilion_phone">(843) 723–0500</string>
    <string name="wentworth_phone">(888) 466–1886</string>
    <string name="francis_website">www.francismarionhotel.com</string>
    <string name="pavilion_website">www.marketpavilion.com</string>
    <string name="wentworth_website">www.wentworthmansion.com</string>
    <string name="francis_info">Built in 1924 and meticulously restored, The Francis Marion Hotel
        features 1920\'s styled décor and comforting amenities. Diners can dig into a plate of
        shrimp, grits, and other Southern delights at The Swamp Fox Restaurant and Bar. Guests can
        work out at the fitness center, and drop by Spa Adagio for a massage, facial, mud wrap,
        and one of the other therapeutic treatments on offer.</string>
    <string name="pavilion_info">Located in the heart of Charleston, this family-friendly hotel
        is within walking distance of many top and historic attractions. Along with 2 restaurants,
        this smoke-free hotel has an outdoor pool and 2 bars/lounges. Free continental breakfast
        and free WiFi in public areas are also provided. Additionally, a 24-hour fitness center,
        a poolside bar, and a rooftop terrace are onsite.</string>
    <string name="wentworth_info">A full-service spa, a restaurant, and a bar/lounge are available
        at this hotel. Free cooked-to-order breakfast is provided, as well as free WiFi in public
        areas. Other amenities include a rooftop terrace and massage/treatment rooms. All 21
        individually decorated rooms feature free WiFi and iPod docks. In addition to upscale
        touches like fireplaces and jetted tubs, guests will find flat-screen TVs with cable
        channels and refrigerators.</string>
    <string name="carriage">Carriage Tour of Historic Charleston</string>
    <string name="culinary">Downtown Charleston Culinary Tour</string>
    <string name="ghost">Ghost City Tours of Charleston</string>
    <string name="carriage_address">8 Guignard Street\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="culinary_address">460 King Street, Suite 200\nCharleston, SC</string>
    <string name="ghost_address">1 Vendue Range, Concord Street\nCharleston, SC 29401</string>
    <string name="carriage_phone">(843) 853–6125</string>
    <string name="culinary_phone">(843) 259–2966</string>
    <string name="ghost_phone">(888) 859–5375</string>
    <string name="carriage_website">www.palmettocarriage.com</string>
    <string name="culinary_website">www.charlestonculinarytours.com</string>
    <string name="ghost_website">www.ghostcitytours.com/charleston</string>
    <string name="carriage_info">Established in 1972, Palmetto Carriage Works is the oldest
        carriage company in historic Charleston, SC. Still family-owned and operated, the
        company offers guided horse and mule-drawn tours of Charleston\'s downtown and
        residential historic district for the thousands of visitors hoping to take in the
        charm and history of the city in a more authentic way.</string>
    <string name="culinary_info">Charleston Culinary Tours combine the best of Charleston history,
        cocktails and food with unique tours that highlight the Lowcountry. On each tour, you
        will not only have an opportunity to sample some of the Lowcountry\'s finest offerings,
        but also to meet the owners, chefs and mixologists behind Charleston\'s impressive culinary
        and bar innovations.</string>
    <string name="ghost_info">Here at Ghost City, we are proud to offer our ghost tours in South
        Carolina\'s most haunted city! Our Charleston Ghost Tours take you to the most haunted
        locations in the downtown area of Charleston. You\'ll hear the stories of Charleston\'s
        haunted history while standing in the very places these haunting events take place.</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="weather">Weather</string>
</resources>
